Guide to the Joni Rabinowitz Papers, 1957-2008 AIS.2010.05
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- New American Movement (NAM), 1971-1985; I.
  - Related Organizations, 1971-1985; 6.
    - Utilities Task Force, 1975-1980 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Democratic Socialists of America (DSA), 1982-1992; II.
  In 1982 the Democratic Socialist Organizing Committee and the New American Movement merged to form the Democratic Socialists of America (DSA), a merger opposed by Rabinowitz. Nonetheless, she was active in the DSA as a member of the national executive committee and she served as a Pittsburgh delegate at the 1983 DSA conference in New York City. The series includes organizational records, various publications, events, and committees and projects the organization was involved in. The series is divided into four subseries which are organized alphabetically. For further information on the DSA, please see the Robert Opie Shepherd Papers Relating to the Democratic Socialists of America, AIS.1990.21 held by the Archives Service Center.
  - Internal Business, 1982-1992; 1.
    This subseries documents the organizational structure of the DSA and includes by-laws, correspondence, financial records, and membership lists which are organized alphabetically. Also included are some of Rabinowitz's personal notebooks from chapter meetings which reflect many of her personal views and thoughts about the organization. The statement concerning "New Directions for DSA" provides further insight into the merger.
    - By-laws, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Finances, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 20-21)
    - Fundraising, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 22)
    - History of Organization, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 23)
    - Membership, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 24)
    - National Board, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 25)
    - National Constitution and By-laws, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 26)
    - National Mailings, 1982-1985 (Box 3, Folder 27)
    - Personal Notebook, 1982-1983 (Box 3, Folder 28)
    - Personal Notebooks from Meetings, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 29)
    - Personal Notebooks from Meetings, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 30)
    - Phone Bank and Contributions, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 31)
    - Photographs Used in Newsletters and Leaflets, undated (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Statement Concerning New Directions for DSA, 1986 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Publications, 1982-1986; 2.
    This subseries contains the various publications created by the Pittsburgh chapter of the DSA and includes newsletters, brochures, chapter mailings (which provide organizational news and announcements), and other various pieces of literature created by the organization. The literature is organized alphabetically. Because the "Robert Opie Shepherd Papers Relating to the Democratic Socialists of America, AIS.1990.21" already contains a significant amount of DSA publications, especially the Allegheny Socialist, only those which were not duplicates were kept in this collection.
    - Allegheny Socialist, February 1992-January 1994 (Box 3, Folder 34)
    - Brochures, undated (Box 3, Folder 36)
    - Chapter Mailings, 1987-1988 (Box 3, Folder 35)
    - Feminist Perspectives on the Family, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Pittsburgh Chapter News Sheets, 1982-1986 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Events, 1982-1991; 3.
    This subseries documents regional and national DSA conventions and conferences, various events the Pittsburgh chapter hosted, and other events chapter members attended. Folders are organized alphabetically.
    - Basic Political Skills Training Conference, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - "Candidates Nite", 1983 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - "Candidates Nite", 1987 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - "Candidates Nite" for Pittsburgh City Council and School Board, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Films, 1985-1991 (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - First DSA Statewide Conference, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Fred Small Concert Planning, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Kristin Lems Concert, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Labor Conference, Detroit, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - Michael Harrington Event, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - Merger Convention, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - National Board Conference, Philadelphia, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 14)
    - National Convention, New York, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 15-16)
    - National Convention Resolutions, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 17)
    - National Convention, Berkeley, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 18)
    - Second DSA Statewide Meeting, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 19)
    - Twentieth Anniversary Civil Rights March on Washington, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Committees and Projects, 1982-1987; 4.
    This subseries documents the many committees and projects that DSA members formed based on international, political, and local issues as well as organizational needs. Folders are organized alphabetically.
    - Anti-Racism Commission and Latino Commission, 1982-1984 (Box 4, Folder 21)
    - Democratic Socialist Political Action Committee, 1980-1987 (Box 4, Folder 22)
    - Feminist Commission, 1982-1985 (Box 4, Folder 23)
    - Institute for Democratic Socialism, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 24)
    - International Affairs Committee, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 25)
    - Labor Commission, 1982-1985 (Box 4, Folder 26)
    - National Advocacy Campaign, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 27)
    - National Executive Committee, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 28-30)
    - National Executive Committee, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 31)
    - National Speaker's Bureau, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 32)
    - Religion and Socialism Commission, undated (Box 4, Folder 33)
    - Urban and Community Commission, undated (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Campaign Involvement, 1981-2008; III.
  This series documents Rabinowitz's involvement in local, regional, and national political campaigns throughout the 1980s and 1990s as well as local political action organizations like Project Vote and Voter REP, The Rainbow Coalition, and the Rainbow Political Action Committee. The series is divided into four subseries. The folders of each subseries are organized alphabetically, excluding "campaigns" which are organized in chronological order. Some of what is included are campaign materials, campaign volunteer recruitment materials, records concerning voter registration, and internal business records from the organizations Rabinowitz was a member of.
  - Campaigns, 1981-2008; 1.
    Organized chronologically, this subseries documents the many local, regional, and national political campaigns Rabinowitz was involved in as a campaign volunteer, director, and organizer and includes campaign materials, volunteer materials, correspondence and press.
    - John Zingaro for City Council, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 35)
    - District Election Campaign, 1981 (Box 4, Folder 36)
    - Jonathan Robinson for City Council, 1982-1983 (Box 4, Folder 37)
    - Jim Young for Congress, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 38)
    - Richard Adams for State Representative, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 39)
    - Election Day, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 40)
    - Jim Ferlo for City Council, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 41)
    - Allen Kukovich for Governer, 1985-1986 (Box 4, Folder 42)
    - Bob Edgar for Senate, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 44)
    - Coalition for District Elections, 1985-1987 (Box 4, Folder 43)
    - Bob Edgar for Senate Phone Bank, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 45)
    - Bob Edgar for Senate Volunteers, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 46)
    - Bob Edgar for Senate, Personal Notebook, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 47)
    - Organizing and Campaigning, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 50)
    - Election Day Volunteer Assignments, 1986 (Box 4, Folder 49)
    - Campaign Volunteers List, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 51)
    - Doris A. Smith Election for Judge of Commonwealth Court, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 52)
    - Cynthia Baldwin Primary Election for Court of Common Pleas, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 53)
    - NRC National Convention, Personal Notes, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 54)
    - Jesse Jackson Campaign Correspondence, 19871988 (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Jackson Campaign, Personal Notebooks, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Election Day, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 2a)
    - Jackson and the Jewish Vote, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Jackson Presidential Primary Materials, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Jackson Campaign, Local Delegates, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Jackson Campaign Phone Bank Volunteers, undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Labor for Jackson, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Jackson Post-Election Analysis, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Primary, Pittsburgh Wards, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Rick Adams for City Council, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Terry Chalich for State Legislature, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Lynn Yaekel for Senate, 1992 (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Rick Adams for City Council, 1994 (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Allen Kukovich for Senate, 1996 (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - 14th Ward Primary, 1997 (Box 5, Folder 15)
    - Rabinowitz and Haer for Democratic Committee People, 1998 (Box 5, Folder 16)
    - Local Primary, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 17)
    - Local Elections, 1999 (Box 5, Folder 18)
    - Allen Kukovich for Lt. Governor Phone Bank, 2001-2002 (Box 5, Folder 19)
    - Allen Kukovich for Governor Primary, 2002 (Box 5, Folder 20)
    - John Kerry for President, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 21)
    - May Primary Elections, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 22)
    - May Primaries and Ward Chair Election, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 23)
    - Presidential Election, 2007-2008 (Box 5, Folder 24)
  - Project Vote and Voter Registration in Pittsburgh (REP), 1983-1988; 2.
    Organized alphabetically, this subseries documents Rabinowitz's involvement in the voter registration activities of two related organizations, Project VOTE! and Voter REP (Registration, Education, and Participation). Voter REP was a local affiliate of Project VOTE!, a national organization based in Washington, D.C. Due to the related goals and relationship between the two organizations, many of the materials in this subseries are mixed.
    Formed in 1986, Voter REP was a nonprofit charitable and educational organization committed to registering voters and increasing the political participation of blacks, women, low-income areas, youth, and disabled peoples. Rabinowitz worked for Voter REP as a coordinator. The organization was located in the offices of the Hunger Action Coalition and grew out of prior Pittsburgh organizations committed to voter registration like the Alliance for Voter Registration. Materials include records pertaining to internal functions of the organization, volunteer recruitment, voter registration drives, newsletters, workshops, and press. Also included are records pertaining to the organization's fight against welfare and unemployment offices who refused the entry of volunteers in order to register people, a fight which eventually led to court.
    - Accounting, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 25)
    - Campaign Analysis, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 26)
    - Correspondence, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 27)
    - Freedom Summer Voter Registration Campaign, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 28)
    - Grant Administration, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 29)
    - History of Organization, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 30)
    - Job Descriptions, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 31)
    - Letter to Thornburgh Regarding Voter Registration, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 32)
    - Logbook, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 33)
    - Meetings, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 34)
    - Monthly Schedules, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 35)
    - Newsletters, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 36)
    - Newspaper Clippings, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 37)
    - Original Proposal for the Organization, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 38)
    - Phone Banks, 1984-1986 (Box 5, Folder 39)
    - Political Workshops, 1984-1994 (Box 5, Folder 40)
    - Pre-District Election Campaign, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 41)
    - Press, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 42)
    - Project Vote Instructions, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 43)
    - Public Service Announcements and Media, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 44)
    - Suit and Injunction, 1983-1986 (Box 5, Folder 45-46)
    - Volunteer Recruitment, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 47)
    - Voter Registration Campaign, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 48)
    - Voter Registration Activities, 1983 (Box 5, Folder 49)
    - Voter Registration for Non-Profits, 1983-1984 (Box 5, Folder 50)
    - Voter Registration Report, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 51)
    - Voter Registration Statistics, 1986 (Box 5, Folder 52)
    - Voters with Disabilities, 1984 (Box 5, Folder 53)
  - The Rainbow Coalition and The Rainbow Political Action Committee, 1985-1990; 3.
    This subseries documents The National Rainbow Coalition (NRC), now the Rainbow Push Coalition, and The Rainbow Political Action Committee (Rainbow PAC). Arranged alphabetically, it includes meeting minutes, by-laws, mailing lists, and national NRC materials. The Rainbow Coalition grew out of Jesse Jackson's 1984 presidential campaign. The coalition was and still is a national organization committed to social justice, civil rights and political activism. It was founded in order to help support candidates for public office dedicated to improving the lives of the powerless. Rabinowitz helped run the Rainbow PAC which functioned as a political action committee based on progressive politics and committed to social justice, democracy and solidarity. Although the Rainbow PAC was inspired by the NRC, they remained unconnected to the National Rainbow Coalition and free from the rules of the NRC.
    - Annual Meeting of Rainbow PAC, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 54)
    - By-Laws of Rainbow PAC, undated (Box 5, Folder 55)
    - Candidate Endorsements for Primaries, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 56)
    - Fundraising Letters and Lists, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 57)
    - Mailings, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 58)
    - Mailing List, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 59)
    - Meeting Attendance, 1988-1989 (Box 5, Folder 60)
    - Meeting Minutes, 1987-1988 (Box 5, Folder 61)
    - National Materials, 1987-1990 (Box 5, Folder 62)
    - Questionnaire Developed for Local Primary, 1989 (Box 5, Folder 63)
    - The Rainbow Report, 1989-1990 (Box 5, Folder 64)
    - State Convention of the Pennsylvania Rainbow Coalition, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 65)
  - 14th Ward Independent Democratic Club, 1985-2008; 4.
    Documented in this subseries is the 14th Ward Independent Democratic Club, of which Rabinowitz was an active participant and member of the board. Materials are organized alphabetically and include the constitution and by-laws, board business, correspondence, events, newsletters and mailings. The organization was founded in 1980 in order to support progressive politics and the principles of the Democratic Party. The club also held forums and discussions in order to help solve community problems. Additionally, the club also worked to endorse and support candidates committed to the same principles established by the club, distributing voters guides before primaries and elections in order to help inform community members.
    - Board Business, 2000-2007 (Box 5, Folder 66)
    - Campaign for Kerry, Edwards, and Hoeffel, 2004 (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - Constitution and By-Laws, 2006 (Box 5, Folder 68)
    - Correspondence, 2005-2008 (Box 5, Folder 69)
    - Events, 1998-2007 (Box 5, Folder 70)
    - Meetings, 2005 (Box 5, Folder 71)
    - Member Lists, 2004-2007 (Box 5, Folder 72)
    - Newsletters and Mailings, 1985-2006 (Box 5, Folder 73)
- Topics and Organizations, 1963-1982; IV.
  Rabinowitz collected an array of materials that illustrate the social, political, and economic issues that she experienced throughout the 1960s and 1970s. These materials provide a glimpse into the issues and organizations that emerged during this period. Included are pamphlets, fliers, letters, press, and organizational materials. The series is divided into three subseries divided by topics, local organizations, and national organizations.
  - Topics, 1965-1983; 1.
    This subseries contains an array of materials that Rabinowitz collected throughout the 1960s and 1970s that demonstrate her interests and concerns; it is organized alphabetically. She kept the materials organized in files according to topics which range from international issues, to labor issues, draft resistance, and socialism.
    - Black Power Movement, 1968-1978 (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Chile, 1973-1979 (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - China, 1965-1976 (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Civil Rights and Racism, 1963-1983 (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Communes, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Conscientious Objection, 1967-1969 (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Criminal Code Reform Act, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Draft Resistance, 1966-1970 (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Health, undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - GI Movement and Amnesty, 1973-1974 (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Indochina, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Labor Issues, Local and Regional, 1975-1979 (Box 6, Folder 12)
    - Labor and Unions, 1975-1982 (Box 6, Folder 13)
    - Labor Related Films, 1970 (Box 6, Folder 14)
    - Labor, Safe Energy, and Anti-Nuke, 1979-1981 (Box 6, Folder 15)
    - Labor, United Aircraft and Olin Drug, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 16)
    - Labor, United Auto Workers, 1964-1979 (Box 6, Folder 17)
    - Labor and Workplace Health Issues, 1979-1980 (Box 6, Folder 18)
    - Marxist-Leninist Groups, 1975 (Box 6, Folder 19)
    - Military Intervention, Disarmament, and Conversion, 1977-1981 (Box 6, Folder 20)
    - National Student Conference Against Racism, Pittsburgh, 1974-1976 (Box 6, Folder 21)
    - National Tax Organizing, 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 22)
    - The New Right, 1978-1981 (Box 6, Folder 23)
    - New York City Issues and Organizations, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 24)
    - Socialism, undated (Box 6, Folder 25)
    - Vietnam, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 26)
    - Worker Ownership, 1982 (Box 6, Folder 27)
  - Local Organizations, 1969-1980; 2.
    This subseries is organized alphabetically and includes material Rabinowitz collected concerning local social justice and activist organizations that emerged in the 1970s and include literature, fliers and brochures.
    - Anti-Vietnam Organizations, 1972-1976 (Box 6, Folder 28)
    - Committee of Concerned Unionists, 1978 (Box 6, Folder 29)
    - Pittsburgh Area Committee on Occupational Safety and Health, 1972-1974 (Box 6, Folder 30)
    - Pittsburgh Chapter Coalition if Labor Union Women, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 31)
    - Pittsburgh Committee Against Registration and the Draft Card (CARD), 1980 (Box 6, Folder 32)
    - Pittsburgh Neighborhood Alliance, 1974-1975 (Box 6, Folder 33)
    - Pittsburgh Radical Women's Union, 1973 (Box 6, Folder 34)
    - Pittsburgh Chapter of Students for a Democratic Society, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 35)
    - Political Prisoner's Solidarity Committee, 1971-1978 (Box 6, Folder 36)
    - Professional Air Traffic Controller's Organization, undated (Box 6, Folder 37)
    - Western Pennsylvania Coalition to Support the United Mine Workers, 1972-1979 (Box 6, Folder 38)
  - National Organizations, 1965-1996; 3.
    Rabinowitz collected the materials of a number of social justice and activist organizations that emerged between 1965 and 1996. This subseries contains literature, fliers and pamphlets produced by these organizations and is organized alphabetically.
    - Bay Area Revolutionary Union, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 39)
    - Berkeley Women's Movement, 1972 (Box 6, Folder 40)
    - Committee of Returned Volunteers, 1969-1970 (Box 6, Folder 41)
    - Free Speech Movement, 1965-1966 (Box 6, Folder 42)
    - International Socialists, 1979 (Box 6, Folder 43)
    - Italian Communist Party, 1976-1978 (Box 6, Folder 44)
    - Labor Party Advocates, 1991-1996 (Box 6, Folder 45)
    - National Caucus of Labor Committees (NCLC), 1966-1969 (Box 6, Folder 46)
    - New Alliance Party, undated (Box 6, Folder 47)
    - New York Peace and Freedom Party, 1968-1969 (Box 6, Folder 48)
    - North American Congress on Latin America, undated (Box 6, Folder 49)
    - North American Farm Alliance, 1984 (Box 6, Folder 50)
    - Radical Historian's Organization, 1971-1980 (Box 7, Folder 1-2)
    - Seattle Liberation Front, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - US Committee for a Democratic Spain, 1972-1976 (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - The Weather Underground, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Radical Education Project, 1968-1969 (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Literature, 1966-1990; V.
  This series contains an array of leftist, socialist, activist, radical and counterculture literature that Rabinowitz collected throughout the 1960s and 1970s. Materials are organized alphabetically and include newsletters, papers, and journals created both independently and by organizations like the Radical Education Project.
  - Against the Grain, No. 1, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - The American Labor Movement Today: a collection of facts and analyses, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - The American Working Class in Transition By: Kim Moody, undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Akwesasne Notes, Late Spring, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Automation and the Abolition of the Market By: Edward J. Nell, 1967 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - The Bill of Rights Journal, Winter, 1988 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - Black Workers in Revolt By: Robert Dudnick, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - Bread and Roses, By: Kathy McAfee and Myrna Wood, 1969 (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - Breaking The Ice Vol. 1 No. 1, 3, and 6, 1973-1974 (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - Buffalo Labor: A History of Militant Struggle, undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - The Contradiction of Advanced Capitalist Society and Its Resolution By: Martin Nicolaus, undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - Cops are Hired to Enforce the Laws, undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - Crisis, Vol. 1 No. 11 and 19, 1971-1972 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - Dayton Women Working, Vol. 2 No. 7, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - The Decline of American Radicalism in the Twentieth Century By: Gabriel Kolko, undated (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - The Demand for Black Labor By: Harold M. Baron, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - Distribution Newsletter No. 2, 1971 (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - Eight Months at Essex By: Kim Moody and Elissa Clarke, undated (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - El Grito Del Norte, Vol. 6 No. 4, 1973 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - El Malcriado, 1966-1967 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - Erie Free Press, Vol. 1 No. 3,9,12, 1974-1975 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - Excerpts from a New Songbook, undated (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - Free West Indian, Vol. 1 No. 50 and Vol. 2 No. 2,10,11,14, 1980-1981 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - From the Horses Mouth, Vol. 4 No. 5, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - Grass Roots, Vol. 3 No. 2, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - The Green Mountain Quarterly, No. 1 and 3, 1975-1976 (Box 8, Folder 26)
  - The Grove Street Grapevine, May, 1974 (Box 8, Folder 27)
  - Health Rights News, Vol. 8 No. 1, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 28)
  - How Harvard Rules, undated (Box 8, Folder 29)
  - How to Counterfeit Credit Cards and Get Away with it, undated (Box 8, Folder 30)
  - I am Furious (Female), undated (Box 8, Folder 31)
  - Just Economics, 1973-1975 (Box 8, Folder 32)
  - Labor and the South By: Robert Analavage, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 33)
  - Labor History Calendar, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 34)
  - Labor Notes, No. 130 and 132, 1990 (Box 8, Folder 35)
  - Metropolis and Movement Life By: Evan Stark, undated (Box 8, Folder 36)
  - A New Era of Labor Revolt By: Stanley Weir, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 37)
  - New Patriot, Vol.1 No. 1, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 38)
  - New Unity, Vol. 1 No. 1 and 8, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 39)
  - New University Conference Crisis Paper, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 40)
  - New York Workers' News and Perspective, No. 1, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 41)
  - Notes from the First Year: New York Radical Women, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 42)
  - Notes on Left Propaganda/How to Spread the Word, undated (Box 8, Folder 43)
  - On Campus in Amerika, 1970 (Box 8, Folder 44)
  - The Organizer, Vol.4 No. 5, 1978 (Box 8, Folder 45)
  - Party and Class, 1975 (Box 8, Folder 46)
  - Perspectives for Radicals By: Stanley Aronowitz, 1968 (Box 8, Folder 47)
  - The Politics of Housework By: Pat Mainardi, undated (Box 8, Folder 48)
  - Poor White Women By: Roxanne Dunbar, undated (Box 8, Folder 49)
  - Power in American Society By: Jim Jacobs, undated (Box 8, Folder 50)
  - Quantum, September, 1972 (Box 8, Folder 51)